本集故事内容包含自杀情节
请观众慎重选择观看
《夏日亡魂》 前情提要
Previously on "Dead of Summer"...
我要走了
I got to go.
我做错什么了 克瑞克特
What did I do? Cricket!
你到底是谁
Who are you?
你说过你会接受真正的我的
Look, you said you could accept me.
-布莱尔 -每次我看到你
- Blair... - Every time I see you,
你好像都在拍摄什么东西
you seem to be filming something.
俗话说得好
You know what they say.
摄像头从不会撒谎
The camera never lies.
我觉得我能和你聊一晚上
I feel like I could talk to you all night.
恶心 她都和你妈妈差不多大了
Gross. She's like your mother's age.
戴伯可能对自己的身份有所隐瞒
Deb might not be who she says she is.
戴伯不是坏人
Deb is not Satanic.
可如果她是的话 克瑞克特不就说对了吗
If she was, isn't Cricket right?
她肯定不会说出来啊
Wouldn't she hide it?
可我确实知道这儿不对劲
But I do know something is going on here.
你有没有想过
You ever think it's possible...
这些东西有可能是真的
that some of it could be real?
那个高个男人说过“这才只是刚刚开始”
The Tall Man has said, "It's only just begun."
SSK字幕组
你希望我说点什么吗
Do you expect me to talk?
不用 邦德先生
No, Mr. Bond.
我只希望你英勇牺牲
I expect you to die.
看看这个 乔尔
Oh, check it out, Joel!
你觉得我能在舞会上扮成007吗
Do you think I could pass as 007 at prom?
也许吧
Maybe...
如果大家都瞎了眼的话
If everyone there was blind.
好咯
Oh, okay.
我会想念你的 弟弟
You know, I'm gonna miss you, bro.
再过几周 你就得去夏令营里了 伙计
A few more weeks, you'll be off at camp, man.
我希望你能和我一起去
I wish you could come with me.
不了 我已经在清水市有过自己的回忆了
Nah, I've had my own experience with Stillwater.
你需要去亲自体验一下
You got to experience it for yourself.
在那当一个讨人厌的孩子吗 没人会相信我和你是亲兄弟的
As the geeky kid that nobody can believe is related to you?
你穿着这个 看他们还会不会叫你讨厌鬼
Let's see them call you geeky in that.
这都能装下四个我了
I could fit four of me in this.
这就要看你怎么穿了
It depends how you wear it.
人们的感觉总能打败现实
Perception beats reality every time.
我不敢相信你要送我你最喜欢的衣服
I can't believe you're giving me your favorite shirt.
等你赢了奥斯卡再来感谢我吧 好吗
Just thank me when you win your first Oscar, okay?
成交
Deal.
这才是我弟弟
My man.
迈克尔 怎么了
What's wrong, Michael?
你是不是 看到什么了
Did you... see something?
我 我看到一个小家伙 他害得我参加舞会快要迟到啦
Uh, I-I see a kid who's gonna make me late for prom, man.
走吧 我得赶紧收拾好自己 小家伙
Come on, I got to get out of here, punk.
我得去冲个澡 然后在豪华轿车到这之前
I got to get showered and get this tux on
穿好礼服
before the limo gets here.
别这样嘛 大家
Come on, guys.
还有半个小时我们就得出发了
We're supposed to hit the trail in a half hour.
-你们这是干什么 -除非我们得到想要的答案
- What are you doing? - We're not going anywhere
不然我们是不会离开的
till we get some answers.
什么答案
About what?
昨晚
Last night.
是啊 你和戴伯昨晚消失去哪儿了
Yeah, where'd you and Deb disappear to?
你们是认真的吗
Seriously?
她 有带着那吓人的面具吗
She, uh, bring that creepy mask with her?
我们一直很担心你
We were worried about you.
只是我们中的某些人
Some of us.
那面具根本不是她的
That mask isn't even hers.
行了 你们都误会戴伯了
Okay, you guys have the wrong idea about Deb.
哟 伙计 你和她打了一炮啊
Yo, man. You totally banged her!
你说什么
What?
不 我才没有
No, I didn't.
有 你有
Yeah, you did.
而且我知道你都录在摄影机里了
And I know you got it on that camera.
来嘛 让我看看
Come on, let me check it out.
来嘛 让我就看一眼
-你们都疯啦 -得了吧 乔尔
- You guys are crazy! - Come on, Joel!
你才是那个和大了你两倍岁数的人滚床单的家伙
You're the one who had sex with someone twice your age.
我们想听细节 快说
We want details... now.
这个嘛 你和德鲁在化妆舞会上动了真感情诶
Well, you and Drew got pretty serious at the masquerade.
你为什么不给我们讲讲细节
Why don't you give us some of those details?
关于这一点
And on that note...
-好吧 -对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
夏日亡魂S01E05
字幕由SSK字幕组倾情译制
字幕仅供学习，勿用于商
转载请注明出处，版权归片方所有
-闪人 -闪人
- Yeah. - Yeah.
新浪微博@SSK字幕组
官网：www.sskzmz.com
夏日亡魂
翻译   方黑羊 默默吼 Alexxx Lynn
校对   Peach
时间轴   络睿
好啦 大家快点
All right, come on!
时间轴   络睿
我们要在高处草地上野营啦
We're gonna make camp at High Meadow!
压制   hhjie
我们要扎好帐篷 还要煮晚饭
We're gonna pitch our tents and then cook dinner.
压制   hhjie
你们在那里能看到天上的每一颗星星
You guys will get to see every star in the sky from up there,
总监   Peach
今晚还有血月出现
and there's a Blood Moon tonight,
总监   Peach
所以会特别壮观的
so it'll be extra awesome.
更多精彩内容敬请关注新浪微博  @SSK字幕组
大家都跟紧克瑞克特
Everyone follow Cricket's lead.
她是我们的户外野营专家
She is our resident outdoor specialist.
选个小伙伴 待在团队里
Pick a partner, stay in groups,
千万不要走散了
and don't wander off the path!
这森林里到处都藏着捕熊陷阱
There are bear traps hidden everywhere in these woods.
你真的很喜欢她 对吗
You really like her, huh?
关于昨晚的疑惑 我很抱歉
I'm sorry about the confusion last night.
如果我们早知道
If we had known...
没事的 不用担心
Yeah, don't worry about it.
我知道这跟我没什么关系
I know it's none of my business,
不过我觉得你们两个 挺棒的
but I think it's great... you two.
谁在意别人怎么说
Who cares what they say?
能和一个人产生共鸣实属不易
It's not easy to make a connection with someone.
如果你这么幸运地找到了
If you're lucky enough to find it,
你就应该努力争取 对吧
you should go for it, right?
对
Right.
嗷呜
Boo!
嘿 嘿 发生什么了
Hey, hey, what's going on?
阿莱克斯说树林里有一只怪物
Alex said there's a monster in these woods!
是的 一只吃人肉的食尸鬼
Yeah, a flesh-eating ghoul
它最喜欢喝野营的人的血了
with a taste for camper blood.
我们走吧
Let's go.
就玩玩嘛 杰西
Whatever, Jessie.
-别这样嘛 -拜 阿莱克斯
-Come on. -Bye, Alex.
嘿 你还好吗
Hey, are you okay?
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe.
我想她需要她的吸入器 就在她背包最上面的袋子里
I think she needs her inhaler. It's in the top of her bag.
好的 我拿到了
All right, I got it.
没事的 放轻松
It's gonna be okay, just relax.
就是这样
There you go.
感觉好些了吗
Better?
别担心 弗朗茜 这只是个故事
Don't worry, Francie. It's just a story.
森林里没有怪物要伤害你
Nothing in these woods will hurt you.
我跟你保证
I promise.
好吧
Okay.
那行 和杰西一起走吧
All right, go with Jessie.
没事的
It's okay.
艾米
Amy.
快给我走开
Leave me alone.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
你是不是看到什么了
Did you see something?
没有
Nope.
我挺好的
I'm good.
可以了 说茄子
Okay, say cheese.
笑一个
Smile.
你哥哥怎么这么久还没好
What is taking your brother so long?
车子已经在等了
Limo's waiting.
我去叫他
I'll go get him.
迈克尔
Michael?
Michael?!
他一直不肯
放过我
好 阿莱克斯和克瑞克特 你们负责柴火
Okay, Alex and Cricket, firewood detail.
德鲁和布莱尔 你们去安排食物
Drew and Blair, get the food organized.
艾米和杰西 我们需要从小溪里取点水来
Amy and Jessie, we need water from the stream.
还有 乔尔 你就和我待在这儿
And, Joel, you'll stay back with me
帮我把帐篷都搭好
and help me pitch the tents.
嘿 祝你搭戴伯的小帐篷搭得愉快
Hey, have fun pitching Deb's tent.
你知道我会的
You know I will.
喔
Oh.
艾米
Amy.
怎么了
Yeah?
小心点
Um, be careful out there.
如何
在野外
生存
真有必要看这个吗
Is that really necessary?
我在员工休息室里找到的
I found it in the staff lounge.
我想应该能派上用场
I figured it could come in handy,
毕竟是我第一次在森林里过夜
being my first overnight and all.
嘿 乔尔还好吗
Hey, is everything okay with Joel?
他看起来有点恍惚
He seemed kind of off.
也许是因为他不像加勒特一样那么疯狂地迷恋你
Maybe he's just not as taken with you as Garrett.
你说什么
Excuse me?
昨晚我看到你的舌头都要伸进他喉咙里了
I saw you last night with your tongue down his throat.
-我听不懂你在说什么 -艾米 别装了好吗
- I am so confused. - Amy, just stop, okay?
我看到你们接吻了
I saw you guys kissing.
可我根本不记得跟他亲过啊
I don't remember kissing him at all.
最近这里发生了特别多诡异的事情
So many freaky things have been going on here.
是这个地方的原因
It's this place.
不 是你自己的问题 别再遮遮掩掩装白莲了
No, it's you. Stop putting up a front.
如果你喜欢他的话 直说就好了
If you're into him, just say so.
如果你喜欢他的话 你就说啊
If you're into him, you say so.
你在瞎说什么啊
What are you talking about?
这里遮遮掩掩的人就只有你一个
The only one putting up a front here is you.
而且加勒特不是你所有老朋友中唯一一个
And Garrett's not the only one of your old friends
不喜欢你这样装白莲的
who doesn't like it.
乔尔
Joel.
你能把那摄像机放下一会么
Can you put the camera down for a second?
我需要
I could, um...
我需要你帮我一下
I could use a hand.
我 我不能把这钉子钉牢在地里
I, uh... I can't get the stake to stay in the ground.
好的 好的 我这就来
Yeah, yeah. One second.
我来吧
Allow me.
弄好了
There you go.
再也没有东西能把这钉子给弄出来了
Nothing is knocking this thing down.
除非是《激流四勇士》的演员决定现身搞破坏
Unless the cast of "Deliverance" Decides to show up.
每次我去野营我都会想起这部电影
I think about that movie every time I go camping.
谁不是呢
How can you not?
想进帐篷里试一下吗
Want to test it out from the inside,
看看这个帐篷是不是特牢固
make sure it's extra sturdy?
唔
Um...
你说什么
What?
我想说 要超越昨晚是有点难
I mean, it'd be hard to top last night,
不过我确信我们能再努力试试看
but I'm sure we could try.
你是说化妆舞会吗
You mean the masquerade?
你真有趣
You're funny.
好啦 我知道了
Yeah, I get it.
这时间和地点确实都不太合适
It's not the time or the place.
也许再晚点吧
Maybe later.
你还好吗 乔尔
You all right, Joel?
我很好啊
Yeah.
只是当你和某个人产生如此强烈的共鸣时
It's just that when you really make a connection with somebody,
那感觉真的很美妙
it's pretty great.
谢谢你 你真贴心
That's sweet. Thank you.
绝对不要把这身衣服弄皱了
No way I'm doing ruffles.
嘿 别拍我 肯尼 我看起来就像
Hey, don't film this, Kenny. I look like a...
大块头吗
A hunk?
你是想说呆瓜吗
You mean dork?
嘿
Hey.
别理他 你一点都不像傻瓜 宝贝
Come on, there's nothing dorky about you, babe.
你看起来像007
You look like Bond.
是吗 哪个 是康纳利还是摩尔演的
Yeah? Which one... Connery or Moore?
拉森比演的
Mm, Lazenby.
啊你真是
Ow! You just...
好了啦 你比其他男的帅多了
Come on, you're a million times hotter than all those guys,
你知道的 我钱途无量的宝贝儿
and you know it, Mr. Golden Boy,
你都被纽约大学电影学院提前录取了
early acceptance to NYU Film School.
你最好让我参演你的所有电影
You better put me in all your movies.
-你还不知道吗 -什么
- Oh, you didn't know? - Hmm?
你已经是我其中一部电影的主演了
You're already in one of my movies.
名字叫《试衣间》
It's called "The Fitting Room."
-别 -来嘛 看镜头
- Stop! - Come on, come on.
你要是想演我的电影 就不能那么害羞
You can't be shy if you're gonna be in my movies.
不不 放下摄像机 乔尔
No, no, put it down. Joel!
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
乔尔
Joel?
你怎么了
What are you doing?
没什么
Nothing.
你不打算帮我一下吗
Are you gonna help me at all?
我也想 但是
I would love to, but, uh...
这根怎么样
How's this one?
不怎么样
No, not that one.
太脆了吗
Too flimsy?
太嫩了 点燃会冒烟 但是不会燃烧
Too green. It'll smoke, not burn.
你还真的是夜场女王啊
You really are still queen of the overnight, aren't you?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
嘿 记得我们以前叫你戴维·克瑞克特吗
Hey, remember when we used to call you Davy Cricket?
嗯 我记得你是那么叫我的
Yeah, I remember you calling me that
而我很讨厌这个名字
and me hating it.
得了吧 你挺喜欢的
Oh, come on, you liked it.
你就承认吧
Come on, admit it.
你小心点
What are you doing?
我告诉过你了 这东西到处都是
I told you, they're everywhere.
哇
Whoa.
这不好笑 你应该当心点儿
Not funny. You should keep your eyes open.
我们都得小心点
We all should.
为什么
And why is that?
因为这些捕熊陷阱不只是唯一
Because bear traps aren't the only thing
我们要担心的东西
we should be worried about.
即使不是戴伯
Even if it wasn't Deb,
我还是看到有人戴着那个面具
I still saw someone in that mask.
这不是我想象出来的
I didn't imagine it,
而且他们有可能还在这里
and they could still be out there.
你知道吗 看起来
You know, it seems like...
你需要点别的事情来转移你的注意力
you need something else to focus on.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是的
Yeah.
我在想 今晚熄灯后
You know, I was thinking, maybe I'd come here tonight,
也许我会来这里 来看血月
after lights out, and watch the Blood Moon.
你想一起吗
You want to join?
你的意思是问我想不想和你在血月下做爱吗
You mean, do I want to have sex with you under the Blood Moon?
我可没那么说
I did not say that.
我知道你是什么样的人
I know you.
也许我变了呢 克瑞克特
Maybe I've changed, Cricket.
又或者也许我是第一个拒绝你的女孩呢
Or maybe I'm the first girl that's ever turned you down,
而你无法接受这个事实
and you can't handle it.
好好欣赏血月吧
Enjoy the Blood Moon.
“选对正确的木棍是
"The right stick is essential
烤出优质棉花糖的关键”
to the perfectly roasted marshmallow."
我有一根
I've got one.
真棒
Nice!
来 我们交换一下吧
Here, let's switch.
看着点儿 兄弟
Watch out, buddy.
抱歉
Oh, sorry about that.
没关系
That's okay.
毕业舞会照的吗
Prom date?
嘿
Hey.
你们看上去好开心
You guys look happy.
是啊
We were.
还在看书吗
Studying up?
多知道点总不会有错 对吧
Couldn't hurt, right?
再说了 你之前好像很担心我
Plus, you did seem worried about me earlier.
是的 抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
我可能有点想多了
Guess I was a little paranoid.
那你现在没事了吧
You're good now, though?
是的
Yeah.
好了 让我看看 你烤得怎么样
Okay, let's see. How you doing?
今晚 杀了 艾米
Kill... Amy... tonight.
不然其他人就会死
Or someone else will die.
布莱尔
Blair.
克瑞克特最喜欢的歌是什么
What's Cricket's favorite song?
为什么这么问
Why?
问这么多干嘛
What do you care why?
是不是当直男被女孩拒绝了
Is this that thing that straight guys do
就会这么做啊
when girls reject them?
快 最喜欢的歌 很简单的问题
Come on, favorite song... easy answer.
布洛特已经给她做了一盘混音带了
Blotter already made her a mix tape.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我希望也许他忘记了某一首歌
I was hoping maybe he'd forgotten a track.
他确实忘了
He did, actually.
《迷人的月亮》 回声与兔人乐队的
"The Killing Moon," Echo & the Bunnymen,
她一直都很喜欢
her all-time favorite.
-《迷人的月亮》吗 -嗯哼
- "Killing Moon"? - Mm-hmm.
好的
Okay.
你有《迷人的月亮》这首歌吗 德鲁斯基
Hey, you got "Killing Moon," Drewski?
去我帐篷里拿
Grab it from my tent.
还有 不要再叫我德鲁斯基了
Also, never call me Drewski again,
不然我就杀了你
or I will end your life.
好吧
Fair enough.
你刚刚还真是酷
That was really cool of you.
听着 我很理解你为什么生我气
Look, I don't blame you for being mad at me.
我只是想说
I just wanted to say...
我给过你机会了
Okay, you had your chance.
再给多我次机会吧
Well, I'm asking for another one.
你告诉我你是谁
You showed me who you are.
我告诉你我是谁 还有什么好说的
I showed you who I was. What's left to say?
天啊
Oh, God!
有人忘了在里面放冰块了
Someone forgot to put ice in there.
恶
Ugh.
好了 没关系
Okay. It's okay.
我们还有一些热狗 在营地那边
Um, there's hot dogs, uh, down at the camp.
我不去
Not it!
我去拿吧
I'll go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
杀了她
Kill her.
艾米 别去
Amy, don't go.
为什么
Why not?
呃
Uh...
她不认识路
She doesn't know these woods.
那你和她一起去
So go with her.
跟着她
Follow her.
等她一个人的时候 杀了她
When she's alone, kill her.
不
No.
不吗
No?
好了
Okay.
艾米 你还是和孩子们待在一起吧
Uh, Amy, you're better with the kids.
我和杰西去
Jessie and I will go.
很好
Exactly.
这是你的选择
It's your choice.
她不死
Her...
其他人就会死
or someone else will die.
哇
Ow!
你看到了吗 劳拉 今天走复古风
Do you see this, Laura? I went old-school.
我租了白色的豪华轿车 还买了兰花
I got the white limo. I got the... orchid.
我甚至还买通了DJ
I'm even gonna bribe the deejay
让他放你最爱的宝拉·阿巴杜的歌曲
to play that Paula Abdul song you love.
今晚肯定很完美
It's gonna be a perfect night.
你想干什么
What do you want?!
你在哪里
Where are you?
我要把这个给警察看
I'm showing this to the cops!
嘿
Hey!
-爸爸 -你还好吗
- Oh, Dad. - You okay?
我 我听到你在大叫
I, uh... I heard you yelling.
是的 我只是
Yeah, uh, I was just...
这个东西 我系不好
this thing is... I can't figure it out.
我有点儿崩溃
I got frustrated.
所以我想着出来外面呼吸一下新鲜空气
I figured I'd just come outside and get some fresh air.
来 我帮你系好
Here, let me help you out.
你得慢慢开始习惯穿礼服了
Now, you better get used to wearing a tux.
今晚参加毕业舞会 明天就去艾美奖颁奖礼
Tonight the prom, tomorrow the Emmys.
是奥斯卡奖  奥斯卡才是电影奖 爸爸
Oscars. It's Oscars for movies, Dad.
好吧 无论是什么
Yeah, well, whatever it is,
我都会坐在前排最中间 为你加油
I will be there front row and center, cheering you on.
谢谢你爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
你紧张吗
Are you nervous?
紧张今晚吗
About tonight?
我只是在想迈克尔
I'm just thinking about Michael.
在毕业舞会那晚
Prom night.
他有告诉过你他看到什么了吗
Did he ever tell you what he saw?
没有 从没说过
No, he never would.
我们不知道他看到什么了
We didn't know what he was seeing
或者说为什么他那么害怕
or why he was so... so scared of it.
我和他
Me and him.
我是说 那没什么的对吧
I mean, it doesn't matter, does it?
无论他看到什么了 那都不是真的
Whatever he saw, it wasn't real.
只是他自己想多了
Just a sickness in his mind.
感谢上帝
I thank God
你永远 都不用去面对那个噩梦
that you will never... never have to face that nightmare.
你确定你还好吗
Are you sure you're okay?
你知道 无论发生什么了
You know, whatever it is,
你都可以告诉我 好吗
you know you can tell me, right?
可能我是有点儿紧张
Maybe I'm a little nervous.
不想让劳拉失望
Don't want to disappoint Laura.
你不会的
You won't.
嘿
Hey.
怎么了 孩子们还好吧
What's up? Kids okay?
嗯 孩子们都好
Yeah, kids are okay.
唔
Um...
但是我不好
But I'm not.
我有预感有些事情要发生
I had a feeling something was up.
怎么回事
What is it?
我以前从没告诉过任何人
I've never told anyone this before.
没关系
It's all right. Yeah.
我觉得我和你心有灵犀
I feel like I have a connection with you.
是的
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我以为
I thought...
你以为什么
You thought what?
我想帮助你 乔尔 我真的想
I want to help, Joel, I do,
但是我 我仍然是你的上司
um, but I'm... I'm still your boss.
你在说什么呢 你仍然是我的上司吗
What are you talking about, you're still my boss?
那昨晚的事算什么
What about last night?
你不能装作什么都没有发生过一样
You can't just act like that didn't happen.
装作没发生过什么呢
Act like what didn't happen?
我们去散步了 我告诉了你基思的事情
We went for a walk. I told you about Keith.
仅此而已
That's... it.
呃
Um...
不如你告诉我到底发生什么了
Why don't you tell me what's really going on.
我想 只是
Um, I... I... I guess I just...
我想太多了
I read more into it.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事的
It's okay.
我要走了
Uh, I'm gonna go.
SSK字幕组
你没法让我消失
You can't make me go away.
我不会消失 除非你杀掉艾米
Not here, not until you kill Amy.
记住 你才是说了算的 好吗
Remember, you're the boss, okay?
别让小小的棉花糖赢过你
Don't let the marshmallow win.
你应该去
You should go.
去赴他的血月之约吗
To his Blood Moon rendezvous?
不了谢谢
No, thanks.
我觉得他已经变了
I think he's changed.
拜托
Please.
他就是个辣鸡 你是知道的
He's a dirt bag, and you know it.
如果他只想和你上床的话
If all he wanted was to sleep with you,
为什么他还来问我你最喜欢的歌是什么呢
why would he ask me what your favorite song is?
他问你我最喜欢的歌了吗
He asked you my favorite song?
是啊
Yeah.
他是真的很用心
He's putting himself out there.
给他个机会吧
Just give him the chance.
你快没时间了
You're running out of time.
别这么做
Don't do that.
你会受伤的
You could hurt yourself.
乔尔
Joel.
杀掉艾米
Kill Amy.
她不死 别人就得死
Her, or someone else will die.
是谁会死呢
Who will it be?
你快没时间了
You're running out of time.
是谁会死呢
Who's it gonna be?
乔尔
Joel?
你的相机呢
Where's your camera?
你平时都一直拿着它的呀
It's usually attached to your hand.
相机没用了
It's not working.
坏了吗
Is it broken?
相机在这里没用
It doesn't work here.
-啊 -啊
- Ah. - Ah.
刚刚那张照得好
That was a good one.
我眼睛闭上了 我想重新再照一张
My eyes were closed. I want a do-over.
你看起来美极了 宝贝
You looked gorgeous, babe.
来嘛
Come on.
等下 你还带着相机啊
Wait, you're bringing that?
是啊 今晚可是我们的毕业舞会
Yeah, it's... it's our prom night.
你不想永远记住今晚吗
Don't you want to remember this forever?
今晚是关于我们的 关于我们的回忆
Tonight's about us, our memories.
这并不需要相机
You don't need a camera for that.
嘿 劳拉 过来
Hey, Laura, come here.
好的
Okay.
你不是真的
You're not real.
你在和谁说话
Who are you talking to?
没人
No one.
呃
Uh...
好了 你说得对 我马上回来
All right, you're right. I'll be right back.
我去把相机存起来
I'm just gonna go check this.
嘿 玩得怎么样
Hey, how's it going?
给你
Here you go.
是的 我能帮你暂存相机
Yeah, I can take that for you.
谢了
Thanks.
我们还在等什么啊
What are we waiting for, huh?
你准备好跳舞了吗
Oh, you ready to dance, or what?
过来
Get over here.
开始吧
Huh?
给布莱尔一个机会吧
I mean, cut Blair some slack.
他 他 他抛弃了我
He... he's... He ran out on me.
那又怎么样 现在他想要跟你和好了
So? Now he wants to un-run.
你完全不知道对一个人那么坦白是什么感觉
You have no idea what it's like to be that open with someone.
你甚至都不敢告诉赛克斯
You can't even tell Sykes
你要上法庭的事
about your court date.
我就是说说而已
Just saying.
那是什么
What's that?
我觉得那应该就是阿莱克斯和艾米约会的小屋
I think that's the cabin that Alex took Amy on their date.
有情调
Hot.
你在这儿干什么呢
What are you doing here?
我在巡逻
I'm patrolling camp
大家都应该去树林里过夜了啊
while everyone else is supposed to be on the overnight,
你们怎么没和他们一起
so why aren't you with them?
我们本来是一起的
We were.
我们
We
我们是和他们一起
We are. Hmm.
好了 我来背这个
Okay. Um, I'm gonna take this.
你知道该怎么回去的对吧
You know how to get back, right?
-是的 -很好
- Yeah. - Great.
你怎么想到要来这里
So, what brings you out here?
我要进去
Going in there.
你想有个人陪吗
Do you want some company?
好啊
Sure.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
就是个旧的猎房
It's just an old hunting cabin.
你真不会撒谎
You're a terrible liar.
这是我进行的调查中的一部分
It's part of an investigation I'm conducting.
什么调查
Into what?
你知道清水曾经是个招魂者营地吗
Did you know Stillwater was a Spiritualist camp?
噢 就像艾米说的那些邪教徒吗
Oh, like those cultists Amy was talking about?
她告诉你了
She told you?
这不是什么秘密吧
I didn't realize it was a secret.
你干嘛这么小心翼翼的
Why are you being so cagey?
1871年的时候这个小屋被突袭了
There was a raid on this cabin in 1871.
这些人追随着一个叫做霍利尤克的招魂者首领
They were after a Spiritualist leader named Holyoke.
湖里的人都是他的信徒
People in the lake were his followers.
他们怎么了
What happened to them?
这类邪教经常会遭遇到的事
The same thing that always happens with these cults.
所有人都死了
Everybody dies.
但是这都是一百多年前的事了 为什么你要
But this was over 100 years ago. Why are you...
因为我觉得可能
Because I still think
还有些信徒在这附近活动
there might be some followers kicking around.
你在逗我吧
Come on, seriously?
昨晚 我看见湖边有群人
Last night, I saw these people down by the lake.
他们戴着面具
They were wearing these masks.
昨晚可是化妆舞会
Well, it was a masked ball.
我的意思是 谁都有可能戴着面具
I mean, they could have been anyone.
可能吧
Yeah, maybe.
但我还是想来检查一下这个地方
But I still wanted to come check this place out,
确保没人在这儿滋事
make sure nobody's been digging around,
有什么歪主意
getting ideas.
看
Look.
这特么是啥
What the hell is that?
在十九世纪人们就用这个来记录事情
This is how people used to record things in the 19th century.
霍利尤克 就是你刚刚说的那个人
"Holyoke"... that's the guy you were just talking about.
就是他 对吧
That's him, right?
还有别的东西
There's something else.
那是什么 硬币吗
What is that, a coin?
是个袖扣
It's a cufflink.
JS
J.S.
杰克·赛克斯
Jack Sykes.
这个是我爸爸的
This belonged to my father.
你觉得她会来吗
You think she's gonna come?
只有一个办法确认
Only one way to find out.
去那儿等她
Get down there and wait for her.
这我能做到 谢了
I can do that. Thanks.
嘿
Hey!
你去哪
Where you going?
去欣赏血月
Uh, to watch the Blood Moon.
一个人吗
Alone?
希望不是
Hopefully not.
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
小心点
Just be careful.
肯定的啦 老爸
Sure thing, Dad.
嘿 谢谢你的磁带 兄弟
Hey, um... thanks for the tape, buddy.
嗯 我也不喜欢“兄弟”这个称呼
Yeah, I don't like "Buddy," Either.
嘿
Hey.
祝你好运 我希望她会去赴约
Good luck. I hope she shows.
谢了
Thanks.
杰西呢
Where's Jessie?
她和赛克斯在一起
She's with Sykes.
她还好吗
Is she okay?
她挺好的 你这是怎么了
She's fine. What's wrong with you?
我只是想确认一下她还好
I'm just making sure that she's okay.
嘿
Hey.
我想确认所有人的安全
That everyone's safe.
没人会安全
No one is.
没人会安全 除非你杀掉艾米
No one is until you kill Amy.
伙计们
Guys.
戴伯让我们现在都过去
Deb needs us now.
你把它丢在哪了 甜心
Where did you leave it, sweetheart?
-你还记得吗 -发生什么了
- Do you remember? - What happened?
她把她的吸入器弄丢了
She lost her inhaler.
如果我们没法找到的话 她就不能呼吸了
She can't breathe if we don't get it back.
不然别人就会死
Or someone else will die.
嘿 弗朗茜 你觉得
Hey, Francie, do you think
你有可能把它落在我们早些时候停下的地方吗
you might have left it where we stopped earlier?
-是吗 -我去找找
- Yeah? - I'll go get it.
-我和你一起去 -不
- I'll go with you. - No.
你就呆在这里
You stay here.
嘿 听着 也许艾米应该和你一起去
Hey, listen, maybe Amy should go.
你最近有点不在状态
You've been a little out of sorts lately.
不 我可以的
No, I can do this.
我必须去
I have to do this.
拿着这个
Here, take this.
以防万一
Just in case.
你还有别的事要去做
You have something else to do.
不 她不会死的
No. She's not dying.
没有人会死
No one is.
你知道你爸以前来过这里吗
Did you know your dad had been here before?
我几天前才知道有这个地方的存在
I didn't even know this place existed until a few days ago.
你觉得他在这里干什么
What do you think he was doing here?
考虑到我们是在这里找到这个的
Considering where we found this,
他应该是在和我们做一样的事
he was doing the same thing we are.
吾闪亮的清晨之使
My bright ambassadors of morning!
此即和平之时
It is time to make peace.
卸下重担
Lay down your burden.
是他吗 霍利尤克
Is that him... Holyoke?
服下药剂 安静前行
Take the potion and step through quietly.
药剂
Potion?
我觉得他是在让他们自杀
I think he's telling them to kill themselves.
相信湖水的力量
Believe in the power of the lake,
它将揭示真相
and it will reveal the truth.
他是恶魔
He was evil.
但他的信徒们
But his followers?
他们对他言听计从
They did anything he told them.
言听计从
Anything.
服下药剂 大步前行
Take the potion and step through.
不
No.
你是谁
Who are you?!
你到底想要我干什么
What do you want from me?!
和我想要迈克尔做的事一样
The same thing I wanted from Michael...
让你服从我的命令
for you to do what I say.
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
你在做什么
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我担心你
I was worried.
你不应该独自一个人在外面
You shouldn't be out here alone.
杀了她
Kill her.
Do it.
现在就杀了她
Now.
乔尔
Joel?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
她不死 别人就要死
Her, or someone else.
乔尔
Joel.
放下你的刀
Put down the knife.
-杀死她 -不
- Kill! - No.
杀死她 杀死她
Kill her! Kill her!
他永远不会放过我的
He'll never leave me alone.
谁 这里没有别人
Who? There's no one here.
乔尔 不要 不要
Joel, stop! Stop!
杀死她
Kill her!
这里没有别人
There's no one here.
一切都会好起来的 深呼吸
Everything's gonna be okay. Just breathe.
没事的
It's okay.
-给你 回家注意安全 -好的
- Here you go. Get home safe. - Okay.
肯尼还好吗
Is Kenny okay?
不 他一点都不好
No, he's not okay.
你打断了他的鼻子
You broke his nose,
而他也不相信你蹩脚的借口
and he didn't buy your lame excuse, either.
我喝醉了
I was drunk.
你只是在车里喝了半杯啤酒
You had half a beer in the limo.
到底怎么了 乔尔
What's going on, Joel?
-告诉我实话 -我早就告诉你了
- Tell me the truth. - I already told you.
我也认识迈克 你现在的行为和他一模一样
I knew Michael, too, and you're acting just like him.
迈克把事情都藏在自己心里 这就害死了他
Michael kept everything inside, and it killed him.
如果那时他寻求帮助的话
If he'd asked for help...
害死他的是他被别人当做怪物
What killed him was being seen as a freak.
他告诉我父母的那一刻
The minute he told my parents,
他们都当他是一个发了疯的孩子
they looked at him like a crazy kid.
从此他们再也没有用正常的眼光看他
They never looked at him the same.
我绝对不会这样对你的
I will never look at you like that.
你在我面前不需要伪装 乔尔
You don't have to pretend with me, Joel.
你不需要是完美无缺的
You don't have to be perfect.
告诉我吧
Just talk with me.
我想要帮助你
I want to help you.
我不需要你的帮助
I don't need your help.
我们分手吧
We're done.
嘿
Hey.
好了 弗朗茜可以正常呼吸了
Well, Francie's breathing normally again.
她会没事的
She's gonna be okay.
多亏了你
Thanks to you.
现在所有人都去睡觉吧
Now, everybody, get to bed.
大家都辛苦了
It's been a long night... for all of us.
我也是时候去赴约了对吧
Guess that's my cue, too, right?
所以你要去见他吗
So you're gonna go meet him?
总要试一下吧
Got to give it a shot.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
看看事情怎么发展再夸我吧
Hold the pride till we see how it goes.
嘿 布莱尔
Uh, hey, Blair?
你说吧 没关系
Go ahead. It's okay.
我要和你们谈谈
I need to talk to you guys.
我一生都努力变得强壮
My whole life, I've tried to be strong.
就是 装作一切都很好的样子
You know, act like everything was fine,
但我还没有对你们坦诚相待
but I haven't been honest about who I really am.
我之前有一个哥哥
I used to have a brother.
迈克尔
Michael.
当迈克尔像我这么大的时候 他自杀了
When Michael was my age, he killed himself.
他看见 一些不存在的东西
He saw things that... weren't there.
迈克尔生病了
Michael had a sickness.
而现在我也得了这个病
And now I have that sickness, too.
我的摄像机曾是我唯一能够信任的东西
My camera used to be the only thing that I could trust
它告诉我什么是真实的
to show me what's real.
它从来都不会骗我
It never lied.
但是现在摄像机都没用了
But now the camera's not working,
而我也感觉越来越糟糕
and I'm getting worse.
什么意思
What do you mean?
有个男人
There's a man.
在我来营地之前我就开始见到他
I started seeing him before I ever came to camp.
我觉得和迈克尔看到的是同一个人
I think Michael saw the same man.
他自始至终没有放过他
He never left him alone.
现在他一直跟着我 让我做一些事情
And now he's following me, asking me to do things.
一些坏事
Terrible things.
比如什么
Like what?
今晚他让我杀死艾米
Tonight he told me to kill Amy.
否则别人就会死掉
Or else someone else would die.
他不是真实的
He's not real.
-你知道的是吗 -这就是问题所在
- You know that, right? - That's just it.
我再也不知道什么是真 什么是假了
I don't know what's real and what isn't anymore,
我很担心
and I'm worried.
如果我找不到办法摆脱他的话
If I don't find a way to stop seeing him...
我会和迈克尔落得一样的下场
I'm gonna end up just like Michael.
我得离开营地
I need to leave camp.
我需要帮助
I need help.
我们也会帮你的 乔尔
We'll help you, too, Joel.
任何事都可以
Whatever you need.
你不需要向我们隐瞒
You don't have to hide things from us.
我们会帮助你的
We're here for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
我错过了什么
What'd I miss?
这一夜真长啊
It's been a night.
我也这么觉得
You and me both.
我在树林里碰见了加勒特
I ran into Garrett in the woods.
他在查看一个旧小屋
He was checking out this old cabin.
我们找到了一个邪教首领的录音
We found recordings of this cult leader
他让他的追随者们自杀
telling all of his followers to kill themselves.
霍利尤克
Holyoke.
你也知道他吗
You know about him, too?
加勒特让我什么都不要说
Garrett told me not to say anything.
他不想我们害怕
He didn't want us freaking out.
没有什么好害怕的
There's nothing to freak out about.
他已经死了 但是他还是很恐怖
He's dead. Still, he's pretty creepy.
乔尔 怎么了
Joel, what is it?
就是他
That's him.
就是他一直跟着我
That's the man who's been following me.
乔尔 如果你的哥哥没有生病呢
Joel, what if your brother wasn't sick?
如果他曾看见的这个人 你现在一直看见的这个人
What if the man he saw... the one you've been seeing...
就是霍利尤克呢
what if that was Holyoke?
是鬼魂吗 你开玩笑的吧
Ghosts? Seriously?
这就是我一直在说的
It's what I've been saying.
是这个地方的问题
It's this place.
这里有些东西不对劲 它了解我们
There's something here. Something that knows us.
是这个地方 它了解我们的弱点
This place, it feeds on our weaknesses,
而霍利尤克和这肯定有什么关系
and Holyoke has something to do with it.
别开玩笑了 艾米
Come on, Amy.
就算这是真的
Even if that were true,
为什么只有乔尔看见过他
why is Joel the only one who's seen him?
他不是唯一一个见过他的
He isn't the only one.
SSK字幕组
那个高大的男人 是他
The Tall Man... that was him.
SSK字幕组
你也见过他吗
You've seen him, too?
为什么是我们
Why us?
他想要什么
What does he want?
他告诉过你他想要什么
He told you what he wants.
你没有照做
You didn't listen.
他说了什么
What did he say?
他有没有告诉你为什么他要和我们说话
Did he tell you why he's speaking to us?
没有
No.
他说了什么
What did he say?
他说你应该杀死她的
He said you should have killed her
你错过了你的机会
when you had the chance.
有人吗
Hello?
克瑞克特 是你吗
Cricket, is that you?